[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "And Casper, did you see him with firearms or were you aware of him having firearms?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Casper", ",", "did", "you", "see", "him", "with", "firearms", "or", "were", "you", "aware", "of", "him", "having", "firearms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I was told that he had firearms and I know of a party that he had shot at.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "told", "that", "he", "had", "firearms", "and", "I", "know", "of", "a", "party", "that", "he", "had", "shot", "at", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Were you therefore surprised or shocked when you heard what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "therefore", "surprised", "or", "shocked", "when", "you", "heard", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "No, I wasn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What was your reaction watching your good friend?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "watching", "your", "good", "friend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, it was pride, and you know just my heart was full.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "pride", ",", "and", "you", "know", "just", "my", "heart", "was", "full", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Is there any realistic chance of, say, a renewal of the assault weapons ban?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "realistic", "chance", "of", ",", "say", ",", "a", "renewal", "of", "the", "assault", "weapons", "ban", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, I think we have a realistic chance at getting some common sense reforms passed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "have", "a", "realistic", "chance", "at", "getting", "some", "common", "sense", "reforms", "passed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Baltimore", "Baltimore", "America"]}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "What was your takeaway from the day and the sort of level of optimism you may feel about actual action being done?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "takeaway", "from", "the", "day", "and", "the", "sort", "of", "level", "of", "optimism", "you", "may", "feel", "about", "actual", "action", "being", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, my jurisdiction surrounds the entire city of Baltimore and as you stated the Baltimore has -- the city itself has seen significant, you know, gun violence as well as other cities across America.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "jurisdiction", "surrounds", "the", "entire", "city", "of", "Baltimore", "and", "as", "you", "stated", "the", "Baltimore", "has", "--", "the", "city", "itself", "has", "seen", "significant", ",", "you", "know", ",", "gun", "violence", "as", "well", "as", "other", "cities", "across", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "That has to be enough, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "has", "to", "be", "enough", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "EX", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Well, I had to be like that way because during those times it's hard and you had a lot of games there, you know, in the area where we were living.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "to", "be", "like", "that", "way", "because", "during", "those", "times", "it", "'s", "hard", "and", "you", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "games", "there", ",", "you", "know", ",", "in", "the", "area", "where", "we", "were", "living", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Sad, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Sad", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yeah, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "So come on, why wouldn't you let your daughter call you dad?", "question_tokens": ["So", "come", "on", ",", "why", "would", "n't", "you", "let", "your", "daughter", "call", "you", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well you had all those kids running around hollering around and hollering, dad, dad, dad, you know, and it gets to be -- it sounds kind of funny to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "you", "had", "all", "those", "kids", "running", "around", "hollering", "around", "and", "hollering", ",", "dad", ",", "dad", ",", "dad", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "it", "gets", "to", "be", "--", "it", "sounds", "kind", "of", "funny", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "But do you have any regrets that you may have been a little bit too tough on some of them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "have", "any", "regrets", "that", "you", "may", "have", "been", "a", "little", "bit", "too", "tough", "on", "some", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, I'm glad I was tough, because look what I came out with.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "glad", "I", "was", "tough", ",", "because", "look", "what", "I", "came", "out", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"], "LOCATION": ["Paris"]}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ",", "RBS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "What would you say to her afterwards?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "her", "afterwards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, Paris is -- even Michael said, she a piece of work, you know, because, most girls are hard to raise.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Paris", "is", "--", "even", "Michael", "said", ",", "she", "a", "piece", "of", "work", ",", "you", "know", ",", "because", ",", "most", "girls", "are", "hard", "to", "raise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Are you as tough with Michael's kids, because he is not around, as you were with Michael and his siblings?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "tough", "with", "Michael", "'s", "kids", ",", "because", "he", "is", "not", "around", ",", "as", "you", "were", "with", "Michael", "and", "his", "siblings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Oh, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael", "Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Do you see Michael in them?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "Michael", "in", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "In Blanket I do.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Blanket", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Las Vegas"]}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Where were you when you heard that Michael had died?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "Michael", "had", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I was -- I was in Las Vegas.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "in", "Las", "Vegas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What did you do when you heard that, after you took the call?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "do", "when", "you", "heard", "that", ",", "after", "you", "took", "the", "call", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Well, the saddest part about the whole thing was, Michael tried to reach me He says call my father.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "saddest", "part", "about", "the", "whole", "thing", "was", ",", "Michael", "tried", "to", "reach", "me", "He", "says", "call", "my", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Did you know he was doing that number of shows?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "he", "was", "doing", "that", "number", "of", "shows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes, I did know he was doing that number of shows.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "know", "he", "was", "doing", "that", "number", "of", "shows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "As his father, how did you feel when he was accused of abusing children?", "question_tokens": ["As", "his", "father", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "he", "was", "accused", "of", "abusing", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, you know, that -- there was a reason why that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "--", "there", "was", "a", "reason", "why", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Do you wish he had never done that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "he", "had", "never", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I wish he had never done that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wish", "he", "had", "never", "done", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "But did you ever worry that the perception of what he was doing wasn't good for him or his image?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "ever", "worry", "that", "the", "perception", "of", "what", "he", "was", "doing", "was", "n't", "good", "for", "him", "or", "his", "image", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Well, Piers, Michael was a big old kid himself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "Michael", "was", "a", "big", "old", "kid", "himself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "You never saw anything that concerned you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "saw", "anything", "that", "concerned", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "There's nothing concerning.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "nothing", "concerning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Or what is it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Well, they've got motives, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'ve", "got", "motives", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Do you still love each other?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "love", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "What's the truth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "ACKSON: The truth is that they had a big fight up there.", "answer_tokens": ["ACKSON", ":", "The", "truth", "is", "that", "they", "had", "a", "big", "fight", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Or are you going to try and protect that, make sure they are not too rich too young?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "going", "to", "try", "and", "protect", "that", ",", "make", "sure", "they", "are", "not", "too", "rich", "too", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "I don't think you can get too rich too young.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "can", "get", "too", "rich", "too", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "What would you like Michael's legacy to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "Michael", "'s", "legacy", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "I'd like his legacy to be what he wanted to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "like", "his", "legacy", "to", "be", "what", "he", "wanted", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "What else would you like to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "would", "you", "like", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I've got a documentary coming out and it's a big one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "a", "documentary", "coming", "out", "and", "it", "'s", "a", "big", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "And what is the thesis of the documentary?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "thesis", "of", "the", "documentary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "\"Journey in My Shoes\".", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Journey", "in", "My", "Shoes", "''", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]